<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science for Nature and People Partnership on NCEAS Training Materials Catalog</title>
    <link>/tags/snapp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science for Nature and People Partnership on NCEAS Training Materials Catalog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/snapp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools and practices for collaborative, reproducible data science</title>
      <link>/events/2020_05_nceaswg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2020_05_nceaswg/</guid>
      <description>Dates: May 8, 2020
Location: Remote This module is an introduction to the data science support NCEAS is providing to LTER and SNAPP working groups followed by a discussion on best practices about data management in a distributed team setup. Participants will have the opportunity to brainstorm on their data and computing needs. In the second part of the workshop, an introduction to the use of NCEAS analytical server and the concept of collaborative coding as a distributed team will be demonstrated to empower participants to develop their analytical workflows in a remote setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Efficient virtual collaboration &amp; facilitation for synthesis science</title>
      <link>/events/2020_04_nceaswg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2020_04_nceaswg/</guid>
      <description>Dates: April 24, 2020
Location: Remote This 3-hour module provides mentorship and facilitation training for Working Groups to develop skill sets, habits, and mindsets to make remote work and collaborative synthesis science more efficient and resilient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science and Collaboration Skills for Integrative Conservation Science</title>
      <link>/events/2020_02_snapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2020_02_snapp/</guid>
      <description>Dates: February 18 - February 21, 2020
Location: Santa Barbara, CA
Venue: NCEAS, 735 State St., Suite 300, UC Santa Barbara
This intensive 4-day workshop on Data Science and Collaboration Skills for Integrative Conservation Science will be held at NCEAS, Santa Barbara, CA from Feb 18 to Feb 21, 2020.
This training, sponsored by SNAPP, aims to bring together the SNAPP and NCEAS postdoctoral associates to foster communities and collaboration, as well as promote scientific computing and open science best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>