<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Collaborative Efforts on NCEAS Training Materials Catalog</title>
    <link>/tags/collaborative/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Collaborative Efforts on NCEAS Training Materials Catalog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/collaborative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Science Synthesis for the Delta Science Program</title>
      <link>/events/2021_09_delta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2021_09_delta/</guid>
      <description>We propose to hold 3 one-week facilitated synthesis and training events for Delta researchers that will revolve around scientific computing and scientific software for reproducible science. We will (1) develop an online curriculum, (2) provide data consulting, (3) include in-person training and facilitated synthesis, and (4) conduct a remote workshop to conclude the group synthesis projects.
The course will focus on techniques for data management, scientific programming, synthetic analysis, and collaboration techniques through the use of open-source, community-supported tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEON Onboarding</title>
      <link>/events/2020_12_neon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2020_12_neon/</guid>
      <description>Dates: December, 2020 Location: Virtual NEON Onboarding A self guided learning curricula to support new NEON postdocs as part of their onboarding experience. The curricula builds from the experience of ecological researchers, trainers, developers and information managers to provide resources and training in support of collaborative, reproducible research practices.
Materials Link to onboarding materials</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>